stillwhite.com 2019-02-14

# Privacy Policy - Stillwhite

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, process, and disclose your information across the Stillwhite Platform. 

#####  Table of contents 

  1. Scope Of This Privacy Policy
  2. The Information We Collect
  3. Why We Collect Personal Information
  4. How Information Is Collected
  5. When Personal Information Is Used & Disclosed
  6. Sensitive Information
  7. Opting “In” Or “Out”
  8. Cookies
  9. The Safety & Security Of Personal Information
  10. How To Access And/Or Update Information
  11. Right To Be Forgotten
  12. Links
  13. Direct Marketing
  14. Complaints And Disputes
  15. GDPR
  16. Additions To This Policy

* * *

Still White Pty Ltd (ABN 98 606 896 842) (Stillwhite or our or we) is in the business of an online platform that connects sellers and buyers seeking to sell and/or buy wedding dresses ( **Services** ). 

This Policy governs how Stillwhite will deal with your Personal Information collected in connection with the Services. 

This Policy also applies to Personal Information collected by Stillwhite in connection with its website, social media accounts, applications and other technological means ( **Online Platforms** ), as well as in connection with any direct communication between you and Stillwhite or you and any other members of Stillwhite. 

#####  1\. Scope Of This Privacy Policy 

1.1. We understand that when accessing our Services, the privacy and confidentiality of Personal Information (as defined under the Privacy Act) is important to you and your customers. That’s why we fully respect your rights to privacy and are committed to protecting the personal and financial details you provide us in line with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to our Services and all individuals who use our Services or whose Personal Information is processed by Stillwhite. 

1.2. We are committed to protecting the privacy of everyone who uses our Online Platforms and/or our Services, for them to understand what Personal Information we collect and store, and why we do so, how we receive and/or obtain that information, the rights an individual has with respect to their Personal Information in our possession, and with complying with the Australian Privacy Principles set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) ( **Privacy Act** ) and the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016.679 ( **GDPR** ). 

#####  2\. The Information We Collect 

We may collect Personal Information that allows us to identify who an individual is and share Personal Information. 

The type of information we may collect includes: 

  * **Personal Information** \- We may collect personal details such as an individual’s name, location, date of birth and nationality allowing us to identify who the individual is;

  * **Contact Information** \- We collect information such as an individual’s email address, telephone & fax number, third-party user names, residential, business and postal address and other information that allows us to contact the individual;

  * **Financial Information** \- We collect financial information such as any bank or credit card details used to transact with us and other information that allows us to transact with the individual and/or provide them with our Services;

  * **Statistical Information** \- We collect behavioral and statistical information about an individual and businesses in connection with the Services and/or the Online Platforms.

#####  3\. Why We Collect Personal Information 

3.1. We collect your personal information so that we can carry out the following actions: 

  * to enable you to use our Online Platforms;

  * to provide our Services;

  * to communicate with you, including about our Services and offers which might interest you;

  * to provide you with information or advice;

  * to process payments by or to you in connection with our Services;

  * to create accounts, tax invoices or receipts;

  * to provide your personal information to third parties in order for them to supply the Services to you;

  * to consider and respond to complaints made by you.

3.2. We may disclose additional purposes for collection of your personal information in collection statements at the point of collection. 

#####  4\. How Information Is Collected 

Information is collected in association with your use of the Services, an enquiry about Stillwhite or generally dealing with us directly or via our Online Platforms. 

The table below outlines how information is collected and/or processed: 

##### __Analytics

The services contained in this section enable Stillwhite to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of user behavior.

  * **Google Analytics** Personal data: Cookies and Usage Data. [_Privacy policy_](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
  * **Facebook Pixel** Personal data: Cookies and Usage Data. [_Privacy policy_](https://www.facebook.com/policy)
  * **Pinterest Analytics** Personal data: Cookies, Usage Data and hashed email address. [_Privacy policy_](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/advertising-guidelines#ads-conversion-tracking)

##### __Payments

Payment processing services enable Stillwhite to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, Stillwhite shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction. 

  * **PayPal** Personal data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. [_Privacy policy_](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)
  * **Stripe** Personal data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. [_Privacy policy_](https://stripe.com/terms/US)

##### __Sending messages

This type of services makes it possible to manage a database of email contacts or any other contact information to communicate better with you. These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by you, as well as when the you interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message. 

##### __A/B Testing

The services contained in this section allow Stillwhite to track and analyze your response concerning web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text or any other component of Stillwhite. 

##### __Registration

By registering or authenticating, you're allowing Stillwhite to identify and give you access to dedicated services. 

  * **Direct registration** Personal data: First name, email address, password, profile picture, location, IP address & wedding date.
  * **PayPal oAuth** Personal data: name, email address & profile picture. [_Privacy policy_](https://www.paypal.com/au/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

##### __Web services

All web servers and hosting are managed are located in different regions around the world, and managed centrally by our team. This includes website hosting, backups, web database, file storage, APIs, and log files. 

#####  5\. When Personal Information Is Used & Disclosed 

5.1. We will not use any Personal Information other than for the purpose for which it was collected other than with the individual’s permission. 

5.2. We will retain Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

5.3. Subject to clause 13, we will not sell an individual’s Personal Information to unrelated third parties. 

5.4. There are some circumstances in which we must disclose an individual’s information: 

  * where we reasonably believe that an individual may be engaged in fraudulent, deceptive or unlawful activity that a governmental authority should be made aware of;

  * as required by any law (including the Privacy Act and GDPR); and/or

  * in order to sell our business (in that we may need to transfer Personal Information to a new owner).

#####  6\. Sensitive Information 

Sensitive information is information about you that reveals your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations, membership of a professional or trade association, membership of a trade union, details of health, disability, sexual orientation or criminal record. 

It is our policy to only collect your sensitive information where it is reasonably necessary for our functions or activities and either you have consented or we are required or authorised under law to do so. 

#####  7\. Opting “In” Or “Out” 

7.1. By clicking “I Agree” or any other button indicating your acceptance of this privacy policy, you expressly consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

7.2. An individual may opt to not have us collect their Personal Information. This may prevent us from offering them some or all of our services and may terminate their access to some or all of the services they access with or through us. They will be aware of this when the following privacy principles apply to us: 

  * Opt In. Where the individual will have the right to choose to have information collected and/or receive information from us; or

  * Opt Out. Where relevant, the individual will have the right to choose to exclude himself or herself from some or all collection of information and/or receiving information from us.

7.3. If an individual believes that they have received information from us that they did not opt in or out to receive, they should contact us on the contact details set out in clause 14. 

7.4. When your Personal Information is included in de-identified, aggregated data, it is not possible to identify you or anything about you from that data. 

#####  8\. Cookies 

We may use temporary (session) cookies or permanent cookies when you access our Online Platforms and/or Services. This allows us to recognise your browser and track the web pages you have visited. You can switch off cookies by adjusting the settings on your web browser. 

#####  9\. The Safety & Security Of Personal Information 

9.1. We may hold your personal information in either electronic or hard copy form. 

9.2. If you provide information to us electronically we retain this information in our computer systems and databases. If you provide information to us in hard copy (paper) this information is normally retained in our files and a copy is made to our electronic files. 

9.3. We use industry standard security measures to safeguard and protect your information. 

9.4. We may disclose your personal information to third parties and service providers located overseas in connection with any purpose, including to overseas cloud computing hosts. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the overseas recipients of your personal information do not breach the privacy obligations relating to your personal information. 

9.5. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any third party (including third parties that we are permitted to disclose an individual’s Personal Information to in accordance with this policy or any applicable laws). The collection and use of an individual’s information by such third parties may be subject to separate privacy and security policies. 

9.6. If an individual suspects any misuse or loss of, or unauthorised access to, their Personal Information, they should let us know immediately. 

9.7. Where we become aware of any breach to our security systems that breaches or is likely to result in a breach of your rights or freedoms with respect to your Personal Information, we will notify you and any supervisory authority as required. 

9.8. We are not liable for any loss, damage or claim arising out of another person’s use of the Personal Information where we were authorised to provide that person with the Personal Information 

#####  10\. How To Access And/Or Update Information 

10.1. If you would like us to update or amend your personal information, please contact us on the contact details set out in clause 14 and we will make the requested amendments. 

10.2. We may ask you to verify your identity to ensure that personal information we hold is not improperly accessed. 

#####  11\. Right To Be Forgotten 

In the event that you decide that you no longer want us to hold your Personal Information, you may notify us in writing on the contact details set out in clause 14 of your desire for us to delete your Personal Information on record. We will use our best endeavours and comply with all legal requirements within a reasonable timeframe to delete your Personal Information, unless we are required by law to retain such information. 

#####  12\. Links 

Links from our Online Platforms or via our Services to third party services that we do not operate or control are provided for your convenience. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of services that are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Third party services should have their own privacy and security policies which we encourage you to read before supplying any personal information to them. 

#####  13\. Direct Marketing 

We and/or our carefully selected third party business providers may contact you with direct marketing communications and information about the Services or other products and services offered by us via telephone, email, SMS, or regular mail. 

If you have indicated a preference for a method of communication, we will endeavor to use that method wherever practical to do so. 

You may opt out of receiving marketing communications at any time by responding via the channel in which you received the marketing communication, or by contacting us on the contact details set out in clause 14. You can unsubscribe from emails by clicking the unsubscribe link on the footer of the email communication you have received. 

#####  14\. Complaints And Disputes 

14.1. If an individual needs to contact us or has a complaint about our handling of their Personal Information, they should address their communication in writing to the details below: 

**Privacy Officer**

Address: Level 3, 11 York St, Sydney NSW 2000 Australia  
Email: support@stillwhite.com 

14.2. If we have a dispute regarding an individual’s Personal Information, we both must first attempt to resolve the issue directly between us. 

14.3. If we become aware of any unauthorised access to an individual’s Personal Information we will inform them and any supervisory authority as required, at the earliest practical opportunity once we have established what was accessed and how it was accessed. 

#####  15\. GDPR 

15.1. If you are: 

  * A resident of the European Union accessing our Online Platforms or receiving our Services in Australia; or

  * accessing our Online Platforms or receiving our Services from within the European Union, then in addition to our obligations under the Privacy Act, Stillwhite is required to comply with the GDPR with respect to your Personal Information.

15.2. Any reference to Personal Information in this Privacy Policy is also a reference to Personal Data (as defined under the GDPR). 

15.3. Stillwhite takes the security and privacy of your Personal Information seriously and has prepared this privacy policy and taken measures to collect, process and hold all Personal Information in compliance with both the Privacy Act and GDPR regardless of the user. Therefore, no additional terms for GDPR users are required. 

#####  16\. Additions To This Policy 

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our website. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy to review any amendments. 

Version Date: October 2018
